Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Hello.
[Money]
[Honey]
Haejun, can I borrow your notebook?
Sure.
Let me find it.
I remember you like apples.
I brought this from home.
Have it.
Haejun, I'm leaving.
Who gave you permission
to accept gifts from others?
Who gave you
permission to
accept gifts from others?
Who gave you
permission to
accept gifts from others?
Have you forgotten my rules?
Except me,
keep your distance from everyone else.
You can't leave me.
Come here.
Sorry.
Class is almost over.
Let go of me!
Why are you doing this to me?
Because you're mine.
I don't like this.
So what?
You can't leave me.
Behave.
Understand?
Let go of me!
It'll be fine.
Please behave,
okay?